Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/hai-nguyenp (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Agile Project Management Programming Business Analysis

Nguyen Hai

Project Manager at NFQ Asia Da Nang City, Vietnam

Summary

Master Degree in Physic, Electrical and Computer Science. Six years experienced in Software Development Industry with various managerial roles and responsibilities: Project Manager, Scrum Master, Business Analyst, Product Owner.

Apart from management aspect, I'm self-taught myself coding as hobby, currently keeping up with mobile app development (iOS) and web development (React JS).

Experience

NFQ Asia Project Manager July 2021 - Present (3 years 9 months) Da Nang City, Vietnam

- Manage dedicated team for an agency with team size up to 10.
- Daily communicate with English speaking client to adjust resources and timeline for their projects.
- Ensure client happy with deliveries on each iteration.
- Grow team in term of performance and effectiveness and aid each team members in their career path.

SUPREMETECH CO., LTD

Project Manager | Proxy Product Owner | Delivery Manager May 2020 - June 2021 (1 year 2 months)

- Da Nang City, Vietnam
- Experienced as Proxy Product Owner in two projects. Single-pointed connect development team with Japanese client/partner. Working closely with Product Owner and design team to define/clear backlog and scope. Help to refine/review specs, consult TL for technical obstacle points. Collaborate with SM to manage team and deliver product increment weekly.
- Project 1: Online ordering web app. Transfer most of features from mobile app version to light web app version and help building proxy server to secure

connection and protect leaking customer information from CSRF attacking. Tech stacks: React JS | Node JS | AWS CloudFront, S3, Lambda

- Project 2: Game community app. Create experimental SNS service specifically for game community. Service is able to integrate with other platforms such as Xbox, PlayStation to extend community circle. Tech stacks:
 React JS | Golang | Selenium | AWS ECS Fargate, ALB, Neptune | Terraform | Auth0
- Project Manager of Big Data project to manage customer loyalty data from different sources through EDI. Data is aggregated and export for multiplepurposes (calculating point, membership promoting, campaign promoting).
- PMO member as Deliver Manager, manage and weekly health check status of company's projects. Support other PM with processes, identify/forecast risk in advance to give personal consultancy toward solution.

Asian Tech Co., Ltd.

Project Manager | Scrum Master | Business Analyst
May 2017 - May 2020 (3 years 1 month)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Education

Yokohama National University

Master's degree, Physics, Electrical and Computer Engineering

長沼スクール東京日本語学校 Comprehensive Course, Japanese Language

Danang University of Science and Technology
Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Automation Engineering